{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043244419","data":{"timestamp":" 947043244418"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" bad20097-db27-41f7-8681-1132a7166e27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043245479","data":{"timestamp":" 947043245479"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" bad20097-db27-41f7-8681-1132a7166e27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043249441","data":{"timestamp":" 947043249441"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" bad20097-db27-41f7-8681-1132a7166e27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043249526","data":{"timestamp":" 947043249526"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" bad20097-db27-41f7-8681-1132a7166e27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043249596","data":{"timestamp":" 947043249595"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" bad20097-db27-41f7-8681-1132a7166e27"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__all.A..Z.asc.uc.4__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043263937","data":{"timestamp":" 947043263936"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_CH-N-A"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043268008","data":{"timestamp":" 947043268008"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_B-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043272301","data":{"timestamp":" 947043272301"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_V-CH-S"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043277334","data":{"timestamp":" 947043277334"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_T-Y-D"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043296024","data":{"timestamp":" 947043296024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_M-K-E"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043299765","data":{"timestamp":" 947043299765"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_Z-F-H"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043307807","data":{"timestamp":" 947043307806"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_G-H-A"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043323772","data":{"timestamp":" 947043323772"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_T-H-G"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043329002","data":{"timestamp":" 947043329002"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_N-I-K"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043332547","data":{"timestamp":" 947043332547"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_B-J-N"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043349134","data":{"timestamp":" 947043349134"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_CH-K-D"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043353795","data":{"timestamp":" 947043353795"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_H-G-L"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043358668","data":{"timestamp":" 947043358668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-Y-L"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043362391","data":{"timestamp":" 947043362391"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_N-S-I"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043365731","data":{"timestamp":" 947043365731"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_R-O-E"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043372239","data":{"timestamp":" 947043372239"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_V-P-W"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043389389","data":{"timestamp":" 947043389389"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-E-S"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043393215","data":{"timestamp":" 947043393215"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_A-L-S"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043397100","data":{"timestamp":" 947043397099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_Y-Z-T"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043401376","data":{"timestamp":" 947043401376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_U-CH-N"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043412657","data":{"timestamp":" 947043412656"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-A-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043419243","data":{"timestamp":" 947043419243"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_F-W-U"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043423263","data":{"timestamp":" 947043423263"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_F-Z-Y"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043429185","data":{"timestamp":" 947043429185"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043434968","data":{"timestamp":" 947043434966"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" eb06dd55-8cc3-4785-818c-6d679889a141"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.75__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_R-P-Z"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043467372","data":{"timestamp":" 947043467372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 993dda33-cfe8-4572-9cab-e818db4f1e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043548494","data":{"timestamp":" 947043548493"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 993dda33-cfe8-4572-9cab-e818db4f1e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043548627","data":{"timestamp":" 947043548627"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 993dda33-cfe8-4572-9cab-e818db4f1e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043614913","data":{"timestamp":" 947043614912"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 993dda33-cfe8-4572-9cab-e818db4f1e79"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043669823","data":{"timestamp":" 947043669823"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_A_A-R-H"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043677740","data":{"timestamp":" 947043677740"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_B_P-B-R"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043681372","data":{"timestamp":" 947043681372"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_CH_f-v-CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043685897","data":{"timestamp":" 947043685897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_D_D-B-P"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043689153","data":{"timestamp":" 947043689153"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_E_T-E-F"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043693125","data":{"timestamp":" 947043693125"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_F_E-F-T"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043720052","data":{"timestamp":" 947043720052"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_G_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043725192","data":{"timestamp":" 947043725192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_H_R-H-A"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043729864","data":{"timestamp":" 947043729864"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_I_J-I-L"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043733556","data":{"timestamp":" 947043733556"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_J_T-I-J"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043737153","data":{"timestamp":" 947043737152"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_K_B-R-K"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043740724","data":{"timestamp":" 947043740724"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_L_L-I-J"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043744192","data":{"timestamp":" 947043744192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-W-N"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043763201","data":{"timestamp":" 947043763201"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_N_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043773387","data":{"timestamp":" 947043773387"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_O_C-G-O"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043785168","data":{"timestamp":" 947043785168"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_P_P-D-R"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043788833","data":{"timestamp":" 947043788833"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_R_R-P-B"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043798176","data":{"timestamp":" 947043798176"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_S_e-S-n"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043804637","data":{"timestamp":" 947043804637"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_T_T-J-F"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043809710","data":{"timestamp":" 947043809709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_U_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043813792","data":{"timestamp":" 947043813792"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_V-U-Y"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043817244","data":{"timestamp":" 947043817244"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_W_W-N-M"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043820749","data":{"timestamp":" 947043820748"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Y_Y-V-U"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043824131","data":{"timestamp":" 947043824131"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043829903","data":{"timestamp":" 947043829900"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ab9bb3a5-d87a-4cdc-9631-3fd95989a96c"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.76__it_20"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_Z_M-Z-N"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043875648","data":{"timestamp":" 947043875647"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043877820","data":{"timestamp":" 947043877819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" a"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043879986","data":{"timestamp":" 947043879985"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Angani"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ANGANI"," userResponse":" ANGANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043883195","data":{"timestamp":" 947043883194"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" B"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043885452","data":{"timestamp":" 947043885451"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" b"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043887710","data":{"timestamp":" 947043887709"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Baba"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BABA"," userResponse":" BABA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043890578","data":{"timestamp":" 947043890577"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043892813","data":{"timestamp":" 947043892811"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" ch"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043894986","data":{"timestamp":" 947043894984"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Chakula"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHAKULA"," userResponse":" CHAKULA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043898275","data":{"timestamp":" 947043898274"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" D"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043900382","data":{"timestamp":" 947043900381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" d"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043902529","data":{"timestamp":" 947043902528"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Dada"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" DADA"," userResponse":" DADA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043905504","data":{"timestamp":" 947043905503"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" E"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043907730","data":{"timestamp":" 947043907729"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" e"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043910002","data":{"timestamp":" 947043910001"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Embe"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" EMBE"," userResponse":" EMBE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043913080","data":{"timestamp":" 947043913079"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" F"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043915451","data":{"timestamp":" 947043915450"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" f"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043917768","data":{"timestamp":" 947043917768"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Fagio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FAGIO"," userResponse":" FAGIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043920829","data":{"timestamp":" 947043920828"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043922952","data":{"timestamp":" 947043922951"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" g"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043925101","data":{"timestamp":" 947043925101"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Gari"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GARI"," userResponse":" GARI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043928266","data":{"timestamp":" 947043928265"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043930460","data":{"timestamp":" 947043930460"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" h"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043932668","data":{"timestamp":" 947043932668"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hunywa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUNYWA"," userResponse":" HUNYWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043935849","data":{"timestamp":" 947043935849"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" I"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043938233","data":{"timestamp":" 947043938232"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" i"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043940691","data":{"timestamp":" 947043940690"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Imara"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" IMARA"," userResponse":" IMARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043943829","data":{"timestamp":" 947043943827"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" J"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043946097","data":{"timestamp":" 947043946096"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" j"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043948375","data":{"timestamp":" 947043948374"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Jua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUA"," userResponse":" JUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043951416","data":{"timestamp":" 947043951416"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" K"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043953665","data":{"timestamp":" 947043953663"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" k"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043955926","data":{"timestamp":" 947043955925"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kuku"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKU"," userResponse":" KUKU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043958906","data":{"timestamp":" 947043958905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" L"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043961255","data":{"timestamp":" 947043961254"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" l"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043963631","data":{"timestamp":" 947043963630"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lori"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LORI"," userResponse":" LORI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043966786","data":{"timestamp":" 947043966785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" M"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043969148","data":{"timestamp":" 947043969147"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" m"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043971512","data":{"timestamp":" 947043971511"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mama"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAMA"," userResponse":" MAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043974535","data":{"timestamp":" 947043974534"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" N"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043976797","data":{"timestamp":" 947043976797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" n"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043979058","data":{"timestamp":" 947043979058"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ndizi"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NDIZI"," userResponse":" NDIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043982345","data":{"timestamp":" 947043982344"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" O"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043984632","data":{"timestamp":" 947043984631"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" o"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043986924","data":{"timestamp":" 947043986923"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ogelea"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" OGELEA"," userResponse":" OGELEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043990320","data":{"timestamp":" 947043990319"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043992756","data":{"timestamp":" 947043992755"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" p"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043995207","data":{"timestamp":" 947043995207"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Pua"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PUA"," userResponse":" PUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947043998086","data":{"timestamp":" 947043998086"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044000291","data":{"timestamp":" 947044000291"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" r"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044002469","data":{"timestamp":" 947044002468"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Rafiki"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" RAFIKI"," userResponse":" RAFIKI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044005898","data":{"timestamp":" 947044005897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044008257","data":{"timestamp":" 947044008257"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" s"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044010609","data":{"timestamp":" 947044010608"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Sikio"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIKIO"," userResponse":" SIKIO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044013746","data":{"timestamp":" 947044013746"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044016018","data":{"timestamp":" 947044016017"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" t"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044018331","data":{"timestamp":" 947044018330"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Taa"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TAA"," userResponse":" TAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044021406","data":{"timestamp":" 947044021405"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" U"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044023518","data":{"timestamp":" 947044023518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" u"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044025709","data":{"timestamp":" 947044025708"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ugali"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UGALI"," userResponse":" UGALI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044028898","data":{"timestamp":" 947044028897"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044031165","data":{"timestamp":" 947044031164"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" v"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044033415","data":{"timestamp":" 947044033414"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Viatu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044036660","data":{"timestamp":" 947044036659"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044038883","data":{"timestamp":" 947044038882"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" w"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044041103","data":{"timestamp":" 947044041102"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Watoto"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WATOTO"," userResponse":" WATOTO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044044414","data":{"timestamp":" 947044044413"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044046765","data":{"timestamp":" 947044046764"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" y"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044049113","data":{"timestamp":" 947044049112"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Yai"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YAI"," userResponse":" YAI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044052221","data":{"timestamp":" 947044052221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044054555","data":{"timestamp":" 947044054554"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044056922","data":{"timestamp":" 947044056921"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044060329","data":{"timestamp":" 947044060327"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044060454","data":{"timestamp":" 947044060454"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 6318cca5-49e2-4eb1-b87c-d6a18393f8ef"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__letters_alphabet_song__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" zipu"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZIPU"," userResponse":" ZIPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044166678","data":{"timestamp":" 947044166678"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 1c9a9294-075f-435c-af56-30629cb67463"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" START"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"countingx:1_10__it_6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044218133","data":{"timestamp":" 947044218132"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 1c9a9294-075f-435c-af56-30629cb67463"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044218336","data":{"timestamp":" 947044218336"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 1c9a9294-075f-435c-af56-30629cb67463"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" Count to 10"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" END"," userResponse":" "," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 2"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"num.scale:0..10.off1.1__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044299482","data":{"timestamp":" 947044299482"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 1c9a9294-075f-435c-af56-30629cb67463"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" countingx"," tutorId":" countingx_1_10__it_6"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" countx_1_10"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" countingx"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" -1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044335641","data":{"timestamp":" 947044335641"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044336024","data":{"timestamp":" 947044336024"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044336518","data":{"timestamp":" 947044336518"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044336873","data":{"timestamp":" 947044336873"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044337285","data":{"timestamp":" 947044337285"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044337767","data":{"timestamp":" 947044337766"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044338000","data":{"timestamp":" 947044337999"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044341261","data":{"timestamp":" 947044341261"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044341297","data":{"timestamp":" 947044341297"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044342024","data":{"timestamp":" 947044342023"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044342430","data":{"timestamp":" 947044342429"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044342737","data":{"timestamp":" 947044342737"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044342954","data":{"timestamp":" 947044342953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044343160","data":{"timestamp":" 947044343159"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044343486","data":{"timestamp":" 947044343486"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044343721","data":{"timestamp":" 947044343720"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044346911","data":{"timestamp":" 947044346910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" R"," userResponse":" R"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044347323","data":{"timestamp":" 947044347322"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" R S"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" S"," userResponse":" S"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044349863","data":{"timestamp":" 947044349862"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" T"," userResponse":" T"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044350077","data":{"timestamp":" 947044350076"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" U"," userResponse":" U"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044350296","data":{"timestamp":" 947044350295"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" T U V"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044353809","data":{"timestamp":" 947044353809"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" W"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" W"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044357611","data":{"timestamp":" 947044357611"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Y"," userResponse":" Y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044358644","data":{"timestamp":" 947044358643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Y Z"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" Z"," userResponse":" Z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044361398","data":{"timestamp":" 947044361397"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" A"," userResponse":" A"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044361782","data":{"timestamp":" 947044361781"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" B"," userResponse":" B"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044362279","data":{"timestamp":" 947044362278"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CH"," userResponse":" CH"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044362633","data":{"timestamp":" 947044362633"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" D"," userResponse":" D"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044363048","data":{"timestamp":" 947044363047"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" E"," userResponse":" E"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044363536","data":{"timestamp":" 947044363535"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" F"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044363772","data":{"timestamp":" 947044363771"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" A B CH D E F G"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" G"," userResponse":" G"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044367022","data":{"timestamp":" 947044367022"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" H"," userResponse":" H"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044367071","data":{"timestamp":" 947044367070"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" I"," userResponse":" I"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044367798","data":{"timestamp":" 947044367798"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" J"," userResponse":" J"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044368203","data":{"timestamp":" 947044368203"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" K"," userResponse":" K"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044368510","data":{"timestamp":" 947044368509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" L"," userResponse":" L"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044368726","data":{"timestamp":" 947044368725"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044368932","data":{"timestamp":" 947044368931"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" N"," userResponse":" N"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044369260","data":{"timestamp":" 947044369259"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" O"," userResponse":" O"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044369492","data":{"timestamp":" 947044369492"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044372105","data":{"timestamp":" 947044372103"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044372237","data":{"timestamp":" 947044372237"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 9d21612f-dc01-4893-a990-729293a2cc48"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__ABCDEFG_EnglishTune_UpperCase__it_21"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" H I J K L M N O P"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" P"," userResponse":" P"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044400953","data":{"timestamp":" 947044400953"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" bc5507c8-5eb5-4990-960b-1f3c16b861e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044401576","data":{"timestamp":" 947044401576"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" bc5507c8-5eb5-4990-960b-1f3c16b861e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044401820","data":{"timestamp":" 947044401819"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" bc5507c8-5eb5-4990-960b-1f3c16b861e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_54__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044402257","data":{"timestamp":" 947044402256"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" bc5507c8-5eb5-4990-960b-1f3c16b861e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044402351","data":{"timestamp":" 947044402351"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" bc5507c8-5eb5-4990-960b-1f3c16b861e3"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_54__it_3"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale zamani sana aliishi buibui mmoja anaitwa Anansi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044426222","data":{"timestamp":" 947044426221"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044436644","data":{"timestamp":" 947044436643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044438242","data":{"timestamp":" 947044438241"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIDOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044441510","data":{"timestamp":" 947044441509"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIDOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044443110","data":{"timestamp":" 947044443109"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VISU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VISU"," userResponse":" VISU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044445929","data":{"timestamp":" 947044445929"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VISU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VISU"," userResponse":" VISU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044447551","data":{"timestamp":" 947044447551"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044450403","data":{"timestamp":" 947044450402"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" START_VIATU"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044453780","data":{"timestamp":" 947044453780"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044455352","data":{"timestamp":" 947044455352"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIJITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIJITI"," userResponse":" VIJITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044458907","data":{"timestamp":" 947044458905"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIJITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIJITI"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044460513","data":{"timestamp":" 947044460512"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VITUMBUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044468608","data":{"timestamp":" 947044468607"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VITUMBUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044470231","data":{"timestamp":" 947044470231"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIDOLE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044473032","data":{"timestamp":" 947044473032"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIDOLE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044474643","data":{"timestamp":" 947044474643"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" VIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044477489","data":{"timestamp":" 947044477488"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" VIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044479109","data":{"timestamp":" 947044479108"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIKAPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKAPU"," userResponse":" VIKAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044481786","data":{"timestamp":" 947044481785"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIKAPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKAPU"," userResponse":" VIKAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044483807","data":{"timestamp":" 947044483805"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" VIKAPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044483927","data":{"timestamp":" 947044483927"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" cc968638-4e2a-4981-ba50-1dd433818803"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIKAPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKAPU"," userResponse":" VIKAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044509187","data":{"timestamp":" 947044509186"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044513152","data":{"timestamp":" 947044513151"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" START_VIAZI"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044514797","data":{"timestamp":" 947044514797"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIAZI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIAZI"," userResponse":" VIAZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044516394","data":{"timestamp":" 947044516394"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIDOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044519299","data":{"timestamp":" 947044519298"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIDOGO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOGO"," userResponse":" VIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044520899","data":{"timestamp":" 947044520898"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VISU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VISU"," userResponse":" VISU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044523251","data":{"timestamp":" 947044523251"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VISU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VISU"," userResponse":" VISU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044524857","data":{"timestamp":" 947044524856"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044527847","data":{"timestamp":" 947044527846"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIATU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIATU"," userResponse":" VIATU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044529465","data":{"timestamp":" 947044529464"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIJITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIJITI"," userResponse":" VIJITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044532316","data":{"timestamp":" 947044532316"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIJITI"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIJITI"," userResponse":" VIJITI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044533911","data":{"timestamp":" 947044533910"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VITUMBUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044537311","data":{"timestamp":" 947044537310"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VITUMBUA"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VITUMBUA"," userResponse":" VITUMBUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044538894","data":{"timestamp":" 947044538893"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIDOLE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044544582","data":{"timestamp":" 947044544582"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIDOLE"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIDOLE"," userResponse":" VIDOLE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044546193","data":{"timestamp":" 947044546192"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" VIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044549050","data":{"timestamp":" 947044549049"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIPEPEO"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIPEPEO"," userResponse":" VIPEPEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044550679","data":{"timestamp":" 947044550679"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIKAPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKAPU"," userResponse":" VIKAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044553219","data":{"timestamp":" 947044553218"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIKAPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKAPU"," userResponse":" VIKAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.parrot::ltr-V.rand.36","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044555248","data":{"timestamp":" 947044555246"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" VIKAPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044555376","data":{"timestamp":" 947044555376"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" 17a48ed9-e4c2-4ec5-9fdf-fca4e84ee5b6"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.parrot__ltr-V.rand.36"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" VIKAPU"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" VIKAPU"," userResponse":" VIKAPU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044579963","data":{"timestamp":" 947044579963"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ff415dbb-040c-4a19-ae48-0e9acd217d72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_Y-B-V"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044583525","data":{"timestamp":" 947044583525"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ff415dbb-040c-4a19-ae48-0e9acd217d72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_S-V-L"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044589039","data":{"timestamp":" 947044589039"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ff415dbb-040c-4a19-ae48-0e9acd217d72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_E-H-V"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044592779","data":{"timestamp":" 947044592779"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ff415dbb-040c-4a19-ae48-0e9acd217d72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_F-U-V"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044595916","data":{"timestamp":" 947044595916"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ff415dbb-040c-4a19-ae48-0e9acd217d72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_J-V-K"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044599137","data":{"timestamp":" 947044599137"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ff415dbb-040c-4a19-ae48-0e9acd217d72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_A-V-O"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044602555","data":{"timestamp":" 947044602555"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ff415dbb-040c-4a19-ae48-0e9acd217d72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_H-K-V"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044605742","data":{"timestamp":" 947044605742"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ff415dbb-040c-4a19-ae48-0e9acd217d72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_R-V-U"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044609219","data":{"timestamp":" 947044609219"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ff415dbb-040c-4a19-ae48-0e9acd217d72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_T-K-V"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044612610","data":{"timestamp":" 947044612610"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ff415dbb-040c-4a19-ae48-0e9acd217d72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_V_F-H-V"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" V"," userResponse":" V"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044618383","data":{"timestamp":" 947044618381"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" ff415dbb-040c-4a19-ae48-0e9acd217d72"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_V..V.all.rand.all.stat.show.67"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_V_F-H-V"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:V..V.all.10.rand.say.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044645788","data":{"timestamp":" 947044645788"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" c05c2570-d3b9-47b0-a084-bcfb90772bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_V..V.all.10.rand.say.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_Y_V"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:V..V.all.10.rand.say.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044652423","data":{"timestamp":" 947044652423"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" c05c2570-d3b9-47b0-a084-bcfb90772bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_V..V.all.10.rand.say.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_Z_I_V"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:V..V.all.10.rand.say.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044659094","data":{"timestamp":" 947044659093"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" c05c2570-d3b9-47b0-a084-bcfb90772bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_V..V.all.10.rand.say.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_A_H_V"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:V..V.all.10.rand.say.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044665761","data":{"timestamp":" 947044665761"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" c05c2570-d3b9-47b0-a084-bcfb90772bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_V..V.all.10.rand.say.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_S_V_T"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:V..V.all.10.rand.say.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044672378","data":{"timestamp":" 947044672378"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" c05c2570-d3b9-47b0-a084-bcfb90772bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_V..V.all.10.rand.say.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_P_N_V"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:V..V.all.10.rand.say.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044679820","data":{"timestamp":" 947044679820"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" c05c2570-d3b9-47b0-a084-bcfb90772bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_V..V.all.10.rand.say.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_P_N_V"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:V..V.all.10.rand.say.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044686468","data":{"timestamp":" 947044686467"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" c05c2570-d3b9-47b0-a084-bcfb90772bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_V..V.all.10.rand.say.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_V_J_I"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:V..V.all.10.rand.say.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044693137","data":{"timestamp":" 947044693136"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" c05c2570-d3b9-47b0-a084-bcfb90772bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_V..V.all.10.rand.say.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_S_V"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:V..V.all.10.rand.say.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044699784","data":{"timestamp":" 947044699784"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" c05c2570-d3b9-47b0-a084-bcfb90772bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_V..V.all.10.rand.say.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_V_L_W"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:V..V.all.10.rand.say.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044706439","data":{"timestamp":" 947044706439"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" c05c2570-d3b9-47b0-a084-bcfb90772bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_V..V.all.10.rand.say.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_Z_V"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:V..V.all.10.rand.say.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044713100","data":{"timestamp":" 947044713099"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" c05c2570-d3b9-47b0-a084-bcfb90772bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_V..V.all.10.rand.say.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_V_O_L"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" LEFT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:V..V.all.10.rand.say.35","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947044725206","data":{"timestamp":" 947044725205"," userId":" 6130000141"," sessionId":" 6130000141_20000105_063340"," gameId":" c05c2570-d3b9-47b0-a084-bcfb90772bd9"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_V..V.all.10.rand.say.35"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_V_O_L"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"}},
{"end":"end"}]}